<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Neha&#39;s blog</title>
  
  
  <link href="/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  
  <link href="https://kagehina919.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2019-04-03T18:44:36.632Z</updated>
  <id>https://kagehina919.github.io/</id>
  
  <author>
    <name>Neha Sharma</name>
    
  </author>
  
  <generator uri="http://hexo.io/">Hexo</generator>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Anime- One of my loves</title>
    <link href="https://kagehina919.github.io/2019/04/04/Anime-One-of-my-life-s-loves/"/>
    <id>https://kagehina919.github.io/2019/04/04/Anime-One-of-my-life-s-loves/</id>
    <published>2019-04-03T18:44:36.680Z</published>
    <updated>2019-04-03T18:44:36.632Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h1 id="With-me-since-my-childhood"><a href="#With-me-since-my-childhood" class="headerlink" title="With me since my childhood"></a>With me since my childhood</h1><p>Anime has been one of my go-to media of entertainment since a very young age!<br>My first anime was Digimon! A great anime that introduced me to the amazing world where the impossible, was possible!<br>It has become more of a hobby and a thing that’s extremely dear to me as I have grown up.<br>Not a single day passes by when I don’t watch some of my favourite episodes from any given anime! They have been extremely inspiring, and I really love them!</p><h2 id="My-favourite"><a href="#My-favourite" class="headerlink" title="My favourite!"></a>My favourite!</h2><p>If I had to choose one, my favourite anime series of all times has to be Naruto!<br>Naruto and Naruto shippuden have been absolute favourites.<br>Packed with life lessons and a great deal of emotions! Covering every aspect of human life, it taught me how fighting for your dreams given any condition could lead to greater merit!<br>It has to be one of the most awesome things I came across in my life!</p><h2 id="A-list-of-my-favourites"><a href="#A-list-of-my-favourites" class="headerlink" title="A list of my favourites!"></a>A list of my favourites!</h2><p>My other favourites include Fullmetal Alchemist Brotherhood, Yuri!!! On Ice, Haikyu!!, Kuroko no Basuke, Code Geass, Fairy Tail, Death Note, Uchuu Kyoudai, Gintama and digimon!<br>All these are worth watching and definitely provide me with a lot of excitement!<br>As I mentioned in my previous blog post, my great desire to visit Japan definitely comes from these amazing shows!<br>They have been amazing and I really love them!<br>New seasons for Haikyuu and a movie for Yuri!!! on Ice are coming up and I couldn’t be more excited!<br>It’s just so so amazing!</p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      
      
        &lt;h1 id=&quot;With-me-since-my-childhood&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#With-me-since-my-childhood&quot; class=&quot;headerlink&quot; title=&quot;With me since my childhood&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;With me 
      
    
    </summary>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Hello World</title>
    <link href="https://kagehina919.github.io/2019/04/03/hello-world/"/>
    <id>https://kagehina919.github.io/2019/04/03/hello-world/</id>
    <published>2019-04-03T18:13:09.792Z</published>
    <updated>2019-04-03T18:13:09.340Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h1 id="Hi-I-am-Neha"><a href="#Hi-I-am-Neha" class="headerlink" title="Hi I am Neha"></a>Hi I am Neha</h1><p>I am a Chemical engineering undergrad from BITS Pilani Hyderabad Campus.<br>I am in my third year.</p><h2 id="Hobbies"><a href="#Hobbies" class="headerlink" title="Hobbies"></a>Hobbies</h2><p>I have a knack for a few things, such as volleyball, which I love playing,<br>figure skating, food, gymnastics, traveling, coding to name a few!</p><h2 id="Areas-of-interest"><a href="#Areas-of-interest" class="headerlink" title="Areas of interest"></a>Areas of interest</h2><p>I love working on React based projects, and love to learn new things too!<br>Traveling is one of my greatest desires as I wish to travel to many amazing places.<br>The first place in my bucketlist is Japan! I really am obsessed with this place and would love to visit it real soon!</p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      
      
        &lt;h1 id=&quot;Hi-I-am-Neha&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Hi-I-am-Neha&quot; class=&quot;headerlink&quot; title=&quot;Hi I am Neha&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Hi I am Neha&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p&gt;I am a Chemical engineering un
      
    
    </summary>
    
    
  </entry>
  
</feed>
